<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creative Innovation on Brian Danin</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creative Innovation on Brian Danin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web Systems</title>
      <link>/specialties/web-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/specialties/web-systems/</guid>
      <description>Professional open source web development solutions tailored to any business needs.
Providing professional solutions for web applications for over 15 years as an expert in Drupal, WordPress, and other open source platforms. With a focus on front-end, JavaScript, HTML, PHP, Google Tag Manager (GTM), and other core web technologies. Committed to providing the best quality solutions that are tailored to meet the needs of any business.
As technology continues to evolve, it can be difficult to keep track of all the new web technologies out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SnowSports</title>
      <link>/specialties/snowsports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/specialties/snowsports/</guid>
      <description>Brian has ski and snowboard certifications from PSIA - AASI Professional Ski and Snowboard Instructors of America, and is a professional ski and snowboard teacher for students of all levels.
Whether you have never been on the snow before or you are an advanced rider, let&amp;rsquo;s connect.
Please contact me for more information or to book a a private lesson today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finance</title>
      <link>/specialties/finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/specialties/finance/</guid>
      <description>Since 2020, Brian has worked in the insurance and investment industry and is a financial agent with life and health licenses. He focuses on community impact and personal financial sustainability.
If you are interested to find out more, start a quote today:
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Please contact me below about general inquiries:
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
